Guide to the Records of the Office of the President (Oliva) RG.3.0.11
New York University Archives
- Series II. Writing and Speeches, 1963-2002; 21.2 Linear Feet in 48 manuscript boxes and 1 half manuscript box
  - Subseries II.B Speeches, 1984-2002
    - International Rectors' Conference, November 1991 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Coca-Cola/NYU Tip-Off Classic -- Alumni Homecoming Weekend, November 1991 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Visit to New York City Council, November 1991 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Reception for Conference on "Sex, Lies, and Politics", December 1991 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Johns Hopkins University Alumni Reception, December 1991 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Carnegie Mellon University Alumni Reception, December 1991 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Bobst Awards in Arts and Letters, December 1991 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Faculty Council Luncheon, December 1991 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Stern Undergraduate Alumni Association Dinner, December 1991 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Unveiling of Portrait of Dean Emeritus Norman Redlich, December 1991 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Naming of Ronald O. Perelman Department of Dermatology, December 1991 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - President's Holiday Party for Student Leaders, December 1991 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Guidance Counselor Reception, December 1991 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Party for Arthur Carter's Birthday, December 1991 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Roundtable on the National Service Trust Fund -- Opening Remarks, January 1992 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Reception for People who Helped with Inauguration, January 1992 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Union College Tournament Alumni Reception, January 1992 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Emory University Alumni Reception, January 1992 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Dedication of the Esther Foley Swimming and Diving Area, January 1992 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - President's Parents Reception, January 1992 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - University of Chicago Alumni Reception, January 1992 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - Washington University in St. Louis Alumni Reception, February 1992 (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - University of Rochester Alumni Reception, February 1992 (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - Brandeis University Alumni Reception, February 1992 (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - Creative Writing Dinner, February 1992 (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - Congressman Bill Green Hearing on Mathematics and Science Education in the United States, February 1992 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Golden Dozen Teaching Reception, February 1992 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - College of Arts and Sciences Dinner for African American and Latino Students, February 1992 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Luncheon for Jan Seidman, February 1992 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Alumni Reception, February 1992 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - NYU Day in Albany Alumni Reception, February 1992 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Torch of Learning Award Reception, February 1992 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - "Science and Mathematics Education: Tomorrow's Opportunity" Symposium, February 1992 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Reception in Honor of Prime Minister of Turkey, February 1992 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Sunday at the Square, March 1992 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Visit by Prime Minister of Italy Giulio Andreotti, March 1992 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Real Estate Institute Urban Leadership Award Dinner, March 1992 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - School of Social Work Benefit, March 1992 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Dedication of Irving and Geraldine Schaffer Conference Room, March 1992 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Reception for Vladeck Fellows, March 1992 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Violet Ball, March 1992 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - President's Reception Buffet Dinner, March 1992 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - "1492: The Expulsion, Prior Conditions and Impact" Symposium Dinner, March 1992 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Luncheon with City Council Members, March 1992 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Kick-Off of Gallatin Arts Festival, April 1992 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Give A Violet Reception, April 1992 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - The Black Church in America Conference, April 1992 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Dedication of the Frederick Loewe Theatre, April 1992 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Tisch School of the Arts Saturday at the Square Brunch, April 1992 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Dinner Honoring Professor Wilson Martins, April 1992 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Reception Honoring John Brademas, April 1992 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - President's Service Awards, April 1992 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Gallatin Twentieth Anniversary Gala, April 1992 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Reception Honoring Professor William J. Baumol, April 1992 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - Discussion about the Sciences at NYU, April 1992 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Kriser Family Dinner, April 1992 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Club Sports Awards, April 1992 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Founder's Day Honors Convocation, April 1992 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Annual Women's Varsity Banquet, April 1992 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Presentation of Presidential Medal to Richard Krautheimer, April 1992 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - 25-Year Service Awards Breakfast, April 1992 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Interdenominational Prayer Service for Carlos Oyola, April 1992 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Service Recognition Reception, April 1992 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Student Senators Council Annual End of Year Dinner, April 1992 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Reception for Graduating Class of Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. Scholars, April 1992 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Black and Latino Awards Ceremony, May 1992 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Guidance Counselor Reception, May 1992 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Association of Black Faculty and Staff Annual Awards Luncheon, May 1992 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Caring Community Breakfast, May 1992 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Distinguished Teaching Awards Reception, May 1992 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Faculty Council Annual End of Year Dinner, May 1992 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Student Athlete Achievement Awards, May 1992 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Community Fund Check Presentation, May 1992 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Prism Award Luncheon, May 1992 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - William Church Osborn Club Annual Dinner Dance, May 1992 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - School of Continuing Education Class Day Exercises, May 1992 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Donation of Hudson River Watefront Parcel by Arthur E. Imperatore and Leonard Stern and Announcment of Scholarships, May 1992 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Stern School of Business Pre-Commencement Exercises, May 1992 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Tisch School of the Arts Salute to the Class of 1992, May 1992 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Commencement, May 1992 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Commencement Anniversary Alumni Breakfast, May 1992 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Hebrew Union College Honorary Degree, May 1992 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - School of Law Commencement Exercises, May 1992 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Dedication of the Russian-American Press and Information Center, Moscow, May 1992 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - NYU in France End of Year Party and Luncheon at Sorbonne, May 1992 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - 21st Century Club Reception, May 1992 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - "Columbus People: An International Conference on 500 Years of Italian Immigration to the Americas", May 1992 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - President's Council Reception, May 1992 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Henry Taub Reception, May 1992 (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - NYU Alumni Council Annual Dinner, June 1992 (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - College of Dentistry Graduation Ceremony, June 1992 (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - "Increasing Minority Participation in the Health Professions" Conference, June 1992 (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - Samuel and Mary Rudin Community Service Awards and Reception, June 1992 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Person of the Year Award Dinner: American Academy of Professional Law Enforcement (AAPLE), June 1992 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Life Induction for Albert Gallatin Associates, June 1992 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Urban Research Center Lecture by Governor Cuomo -- "The Importance of Immigration to New York", June 1992 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Governor's Committee on Scholastic Achievement Scholarship Awards Ceremony, June 1992 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Grey Art Gallery Out of the Opulent Past Preview, June 1992 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Charles Waldo Haskins Award Dinner -- Stern School of Business, June 1992 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - University of Houston Luncheon, June 1992 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Enrollment Services Luncheon, June 1992 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Dinner Honoring Kitty Carlisle Hart, June 1992 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Faculty Experts Reception, June 1992 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - End-of-Year Reception for Schools, July 1992 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Reception for Kristina Brewer, August 1992 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Student Life Barbeque, August 1992 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Prime Minister of Ireland Visit, September 1992 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Reception for University Professors and Endowed Chairs -- Part I, September 1992 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Community Welcome Reception, September 1992 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Italian Welfare League Award, September 1992 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Reception for University Professors and Endowed Chairs -- Part II, September 1992 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - WNYU Steering Committee Meeting, September 1992 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Tour of Skirball Institute of Biomolecular Medicine, October 1992 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Mediating History Book Party, October 1992 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - NYU New Jersey Alumni Association Dinner, October 1992 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Investors in Excellence Reception, October 1992 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Annual Dinner of the Alumni Federation and the Medallion Society, October 1992 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Italian-American Heritage Celebration, October 1992 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Bill Green Neural Science Luncheon, October 1992 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Luncheon for Martin Luther King, Jr. Scholars and Opportunity Fellows, October 1992 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Opening Reception for Giovanni Battista Piranesi: Roman Antiquities from the Republican Era Exhibition, October 1992 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Parent's Day President's Luncheon, October 1992 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Varsity Club Annual Awards Dinner, October 1992 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Reception for New Faculty, October 1992 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Carlos Oyola Scholarship Reception, October 1992 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Italian Chamber of Commerce, November 1992 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - NYU Protection Department Awards Ceremony, November 1992 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - MacCracken Awards Reception, November 1992 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Scholarship Luncheon, November 1992 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - "God's Trombones: Seven Negro Sermons in Verse, Tribute to James Weldon Johnson", November 1992 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Stop-By at SEHNAP -- Discussion with Alan Menken, November 1992 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Presidential Meet the Press Dinner, November 1992 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - 7th Annual Alumni Federation Finance Forum, November 1992 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - South Asian Festival Closing Ceremony, November 1992 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - "The Anatomy of Hate" Conference Opening Session, November 1992 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Discussion with U.S. Representative Charles Rangel, November 1992 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Dinner Honoring Arthur E. Imperatore and Leonard Stern, November 1992 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Morning at Washington Square: A Day for African-American and Latino Students, November 1992 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Presentation of Onassis Center Medal for Excellence in Hellenic Studies to Homer A. Thompson, November 1992 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Fall Unity Social -- "Building Bridges: Unity through Community", November 1992 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Tri-State Counselor Reception, December 1992 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Holiday Party for Student Leaders, December 1992 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Presidential Lecture Introduction for Tony Judt, December 1992 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - C-Team Holiday Party, December 1992 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - "Women's Options for the Future" Seminar, December 1992 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Bobst Awards, December 1992 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Office of International Student Services, December 1992 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Washington Square Windows Awards Ceremony, December 1992 (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Lecture by Governor Mario Cuomo -- "The Real New York", December 1992 (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Case Western Reserve University Alumni Reception, January 1993 (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Carnegie Mellon University Alumni Reception, January 1993 (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Brandeis University Alumni Reception, January 1993 (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - University of Rochester Alumni Reception, January 1993 (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - Tribute to Russell Niles, January 1993 (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - Barbara Lubin Goldsmith Dinner, January 1993 (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - Faculty Resource Network Student Exchange Reception, January 1993 (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - Dinner for Shigekuni Kawamura, February 1993 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Women for Women Luncheon, February 1993 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Asian Pride Awards Ceremony, February 1993 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Reception Honoring Professor Neil Postman, February 1993 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Washington University in St. Louis Alumni Reception, February 1993 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - University of Chicago Alumni Reception, February 1993 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - College of Arts and Sciences Dinner for Prospective African American and Latino Students, February 1993 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - NYU Day in Albany Alumni Reception and Luncheon with Alumni State Legislators, February 1993 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Emory University Alumni Reception, February 1993 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - C-Team Reception, March 1993 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Sunday at the Square, March 1993 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Commission on Independent Colleges and Universities (CICU) Annual Meeting, March 1993 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Real Estate Institute Urban Leadership Award Dinner, March 1993 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Torch of Learning Award Luncheon, March 1993 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Dedication of Brown Building as National Historic Landmark and Commemoration of the Triangle Shirtwaist Fire, March 1993 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Recently Named Chaired Professors Reception, March 1993 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Memorial Tribute to Howard "Jake" Cann, March 1993 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Violet Ball, March 1993 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Greeting for Presidential Lecturer Lea Brilmeyer, March 1993 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Caring Community Breakfast, April 1993 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Urban Community College Leadership Cocktail Party and Dinner, April 1993 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Tisch School of the Arts Saturday at the Square Brunch, April 1993 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Reception for Muriel Mantel in Honor of Her Retirement, April 1993 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - NYU Celebrates 120 Years of Choral Singing Presented by the Choral Alumni Club, April 1993 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Founder's Day, April 1993 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Rectors Conference, April 1993 (Box 35, Folder 26-27)
    - President's Service Awards, April 1993 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Stern Management Education Center Dedication Ceremony, April 1993 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Ireland House Dedication, April 1993 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Annual Women's Varsity Banquet, April 1993 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Village Improvement Program Day and Fountain Dedication, April 1993 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Kriser Family Dinner, April 1993 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Student Athlete Achievement Awards, April 1993 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Greeting to Guidance Counselors, May 1993 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - 25-Year Service Awards Breakfast, May 1993 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Service Recognition Reception, May 1993 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Community Fund Check Presentation, May 1993 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Prism Award Luncheon, May 1993 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Give A Violet Reception, May 1993 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Press Conference and Luncheon for Lennart Philipson, May 1993 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Reception for Graduating Class of Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. Scholars, May 1993 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - C-Team Reception, May 1993 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - SEHNAP Valedictory Ceremony, May 1993 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - School of Continuing Education Class Day Exercises, May 1993 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Stern School Undergraduate Pre-Commencement Exercises, May 1993 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Tisch School of the Arts Salute to the Class of 1993, May 1993 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - College of Arts and Sciences Class Night, May 1993 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Commencement, May 1993 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Commencement Anniversary Alumni Breakfast, May 1993 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - School of Medicine Last Day Exercises, May 1993 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - School of Law Convocation, May 1993 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - President's Council Reception, May 1993 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Rita and Stanley Kaplan Luncheon, May 1993 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Dinner Honoring Roscoe C. Brown, Jr., May 1993 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - John Revere Society Reception and Dinner, May 1993 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Alumni Council Dinner, June 1993 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Henry James Conference Welcome, June 1993 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Robert F. Wagner Public Service Awards Dinner, June 1993 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Faculty Resource Network Reception, June 1993 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - College of Dentistry Commencement, June 1993 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - 8th Congressional District Community Conference -- "Health Care in the 21st Century", June 1993 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Farewell Dinner for Daithi O'Ceallaigh, June 1993 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Honorary Degree from University College Dublin -- Luncheon, June 1993 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Charles Waldo Haskins Award Dinner -- Stern School of Business, June 1993 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - President's Welcome Picnic, September 1993 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Reception to Celebrate Publication of Greenwich Village: Culture and Counterculture, September 1993 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Introduction for Presidential Lecturer Manthia Diawara, September 1993 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Greenberg Hall Dedication, September 1993 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Grand Opening of Loeb Food Court, September 1993 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Stern School Dinner for George Daly, September 1993 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Dinner Honoring Rita Hillman, September 1993 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Visit of Italian Minister of Foreign Affairs Beniamino Andreatta, October 1993 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - University of Amsterdam UNICA Meeting, October 1993 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Westchester Alumni Event, October 1993 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - New York Archives Week, October 1993 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Tougaloo College Faculty Awards Banquet, October 1993 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Reception Honoring Brian Friel, October 1993 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Skirball Institute Dinner -- Biomolecular Building Dedication, October 1993 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Alumni Federation and Medallion Society Annual Dinner, October 1993 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. Scholars Reception, October 1993 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Parents' Day President's Luncheon, October 1993 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - New Faculty Reception, October 1993 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Varsity Club Reunion, October 1993 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - MacCracken Reception, October 1993 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Citicorp Luncheon, November 1993 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Law School Campaign Kick-Off Dinner, November 1993 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - School of Law Campaign Kick-Off Brunch, November 1993 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Tribute to Dean Dick West, November 1993 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - NYU Musical Theatre Hall of Fame Ribbon-Cutting, November 1993 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - President's Meet the Press Dinner, November 1993 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Reception for Visiting Russian Scholars, November 1993 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Retirement Party for Walter Murray, November 1993 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Byzantium and the Balkans Conference -- Onassis Center, November 1993 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Retirement Party for Allen Claxton, November 1993 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Morning at Washington Square, November 1993 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Alumni Federation Finance Forum, November 1993 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Evenings at Washington Square with Police Commissioner Ray Kelly, November 1993 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Luncheon for Charles Simon, November 1993 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Reception in Honor of Ramon Cortines, November 1993 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Breakfast for Assemblyman Edward Griffith, December 1993 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - C-Team Holiday Party, December 1993 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Regional Guidance Counselor's Reception, December 1993 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Reception for Earl Davis (with Association of Black Faculty and Staff), December 1993 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Alumni Basketball Game and Announcement of Gift from Adolph Schayes, December 1993 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - University of Rochester Alumni Reception, December 1993 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Holiday Party for Student Leaders, December 1993 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Police Athletic League (PAL) Awards Ceremony -- "Stories My Grandparents Told Me", December 1993 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - President's Office Holiday Party, December 1993 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Dinner for Earl Davis, December 1993 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Press Conference and Reception for Ray Kelly, January 1994 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Union College Reception and Tournament, January 1994 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Emory University Alumni Reception, January 1994 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Carnegie Mellon University Alumni Reception, January 1994 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Faculty Resource Network Reception, January 1994 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - EQUAL Commission Reception, January 1994 (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Introduction of Antonio Di Pietro, January 1994 (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Brandeis University Alumni Reception, February 1994 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - Memorial for W. Edward Deming, February 1994 (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - Palm Beach Development Presidential Luncheon, February 1994 (Box 39, Folder 30)
    - Stop-By Martin Gruber Reception, February 1994 (Box 39, Folder 31)
    - Memorial for Robert F. Wagner, Jr., February 1994 (Box 39, Folder 32)
    - University of Chicago Alumni Reception, February 1994 (Box 39, Folder 33)
    - Washington University in St. Louis Alumni Reception, February 1994 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Torch of Learning Award Luncheon, February 1994 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Mega Cities Leadership Training Project and Awards Dinner, February 1994 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - NYU in Albany Day Alumni Reception, March 1994 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Sunday at the Square, March 1994 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Introduction for Presidential Lecturer Sylvia Molloy, March 1994 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Real Estate Institute Urban Leadership Award Dinner, March 1994 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Lecture and Dinner for Henry Louis Gates, March 1994 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Heyman Hall Dedication, March 1994 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Investors in Excellence Luncheon, March 1994 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Dinner Honoring Sylvia Molloy, March 1994 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - New York State Commission on National and Community Service Public Hearing, March 1994 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - School of Social Work Annual Benefit Dinner, March 1994 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - "Black Cinema: A Celebration of Pan-African Film" Conference Welcome, March 1994 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Martin Scorsese Dinner, March 1994 (Box 40, Folder 15)